{
    "id": "f6b6ced99a5b4303bd6e4a2bdbc71563",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… to him yesterday.",
            "description": "To simply say that something happened in the past, use the simple past. ",
            "answers": [
                "wrote",
                "have written",
                "had written"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72371b102ea94c1b8bc5e6ce89afc93f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… to the boys about my holiday.",
            "description": "We normally use the present perfect to talk about a finished event, when there is no time expression. ",
            "answers": [
                "spoke",
                "had spoken",
                "have spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "44e8bc0781ea42719f425cd9f9524dd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… him yesterday.",
            "description": "Use the simple past to say that something happened in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "have seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ad4ce14bfc347f4a2f013d6d64333c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………… the job a week ago.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to say that something happened sometime ago. ",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "have finished",
                "had finished"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6f12294b74d04a30ac9f821e065b1217"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………. under the tree motionless.",
            "description": "Lay is the past participle of lie. ",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "has lain",
                "has laid"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76899546162d49c49b2eb2d300888446"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………… here a moment ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b7077c518bc42e092fd37d8ef2ebf5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………….. to the movies last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f93ce8a389249219ac5c01b8019e2e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I reached home, he ………………………… his lunch.",
            "description": "The past continuous is used to talk about an activity that was going on at a particular point of time in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "is having",
                "was having"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "26fee47980f64cc987f8dcae5d82dc18"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ……………………….. her the previous day.",
            "description": "The past perfect is used to talk about the earlier of two past actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "has seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cf54243663344b38873e964a565c3cd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………….. before they found her.",
            "description": "The past perfect is used to talk about the earlier of two past actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "has died",
                "had died"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cc8a07eba2f944daa3fd1aedcd4f8da2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. you for a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not meet",
                "have not met",
                "had not met"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2f149ec2e0e455caf6b9f83b12f528d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although the driver was badly hurt, he was able to explain what ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "happened",
                "has happened",
                "had happened"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "04659eed8a34467a98762982fe5e4342"
        }
    ]
}